Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence: Gilbertson, Eric, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0039, Folder 35)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence: Nester, William, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 1)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence: Robinson, Ted, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 2)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Council on Student Affairs: Minutes, 1974 December-1976 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 3)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Drowning Incident of Matthews, Hannah, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 4)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Fraternities and Sororities, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 5)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Garrett, Darwitt: Illegal Scheduling Procedures, 1978 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 6)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Health Insurance Policies, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 7)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Homosexuality, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 8)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Muhammad Ali Contract Dispute, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 9)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Musical Chairs Game/Fund Raiser, 1980 April-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 10)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Procedures for Hearing Cases in Violation of Rule 51.03, 1973 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 11)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Proposal for a Student Store, 1974 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 12)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: A Proposal for Women's Services by B. Archibald, 1974 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 13)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Proposed Budget and Staffing Requirements for the University Environmental and Occupational Safety and Health (EOSH) Program, 1979 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 14)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Proposed Changes in Code of Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 15)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Rape Prevention Program, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 16)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: AdHoc Committee Report on Majority Age 18, 1973 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 17)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: "Alternative to Hell Week" By B.J. Tootle, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 18)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Career Development Services Committee, 1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 19)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Fall Quarter Welcome Program, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 20)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Intrafraternity Council Annual Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 21)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Kaufman Report on Student Affairs, 1973 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 22)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Mental Health Committee, 1979 April-September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 23)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Monthly Reports of Student Services, 1973 November-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 24)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Monthly Reports on Student Services, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 25)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Monthly Reports on Student Services, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 26)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Monthly Reports on Student Services, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 27)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Monthly Reports on Student Services, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 28)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Monthly Reports on Student Services, 1978 January-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 29)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Monthly Reports on Student Services, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 30)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Office of the V.P. for Student Services Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 31)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: OSU Dormitory Revenue Bond Funds, 1978 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 32)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Policy Committee on Food Service, 1974 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 33)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: RSC Audit Findings, 1974 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 34)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: University Health Service: OSU, 1972 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 35)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Quarterly, 1978 Fall-1980 Fall (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 36)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Revolutionary Communist Youth Brigade, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 37)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Rock Concerts, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 38)
  - Student Services: Vice-president for: Reports: Search for New Vice-President, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 39)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Student Deaths, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 40)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Student Rights, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 41)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Summer Orientation Program, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 42)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: Travel Services, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 43)
  - Student Services: Vice-President for: Reports: University Health Service Budget, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 44)
  - Student Statistical Services: Office of: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 45)
  - Student Unions: Ohio/Drake, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 46)
  - Sullivant Medal: Correspondence (Incl. History), 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 47)
  - Task Force: Minority Report, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 48)
  - Task Force: Needs of the Physically Handicapped, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 49)
  - Research at OSU: Status and Recommendations for Improvements, 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 50)
  - Taylor, Fred: Basketball Coach: Resignation of: Correspondence, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 51)
  - Teaching Staff: Conference Committee on, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 52)
  - Telecommunications Center: Committee, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 53)
  - Telecommunications Center: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 54)
  - Telecommunications Center: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 55)
  - Telecommunications Center: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 56)
  - Telecommunications Center: President's Conference, 1979 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 57)
  - Telecommunications Center: Search for Associate Director, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0040, Folder 58)
  - Telecommunications Center Libraries: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Committee: Report, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 2)
  - Thurber Theater: Dedication, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 3)
  - Title IX, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 4)
  - Title IX, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 5)
  - Title IX, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 6)
  - Title IX: Compliance at the OSU Athletic Dept.: Special Report, 1976 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 7)
  - Title VII: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 8)
  - Toxic Wastes: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 9)
  - Traffic Improvements: Memos, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 10)
  - Traffic and Parking: Commission on: Minutes (Incl. Memos), 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 11)
  - Traffic and Parking: Commission on: Reports, 1973 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 12)
  - Traffic and Parking: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 13)
  - Traffic and Parking: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer: Search for, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 15)
  - Truth in Testing: Tuition: See fees, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 16)
  - Tuition Tax Credit: Correspondence, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 1977 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Student Government, 1973 February-1980 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 19)
  - US Bicentennial Commission: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 20)
  - US Dept of Health, Education and Welfare: Application for Cooperative Education Programs, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 21)
  - US Dept of Health, Education and Welfare: Correspondence, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 22)
  - US Dept of Health, Education, and Welfare: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 23)
  - US Dept of Health, Education and Welfare: Equal Employment Opportunity: Report to Enarson, 1972 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 24)
  - US Dept of Health, Education and Welfare: Meeting with Califano on Higher Education, 1979 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 25)
  - US Dept. of Labor: Affirmative Action Program, 1978 December-1979 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 26)
  - US Dept of Labor: Allegations Files by the Women's Caucus, 1980 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 27)
  - US Dept of Labor: Fair Labor Standards, 1980 May-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 28)
  - US Dept of Labor: Handicap Discrimination, 1980 January-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 29)
  - US Dept of Labor: Race/Color Discrimination, 1980 February-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 30)
  - US Dept of Labor: Sex Discrimination, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 31)
  - US Federal Government: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 32)
  - US Federal Government: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 33)
  - US Federal Government: Correspondence, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0041, Folder 34)
  - US Federal Government: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 1)
  - United Way Campaign, 1971-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 2)
  - United Way Campaign, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 3)
  - Universities Council on Water Resources:Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 4)
  - Universities Space Research Association: Correspondence, 1971 February-1974 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 5)
  - Universities Space Research Association: Minutes, 1972 April-1974 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 6)
  - University Activities Center, 1973 February-1975 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 7)
  - University Calendar, 1973 January-1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 8)
  - University College: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 9)
  - University College: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 10)
  - University College: Correspondence, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 11)
  - University College: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 12)
  - University College: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 13)
  - University College: Developmental Education Annual for Fiscal Year, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 14)
  - University College: Report to the Ohio Board of Regents: Fiscal Year, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 15)
  - University Community Profile: Report, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 16)
  - University Development: Office of: Automobile Donation, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 17)
  - University Development: Office of: Correspondence, 1972 January-1973 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 18)
  - University Development: Office of: Faculty and Staff Services, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 19)
  - University Development: Office of: Funding, 1969 December-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 20)
  - University Development: Office of: Monthly Reports, 1972 September-1973 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 21)
  - University Development: Office of: Monthly Reports, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 22)
  - University Development: Office of: Monthly Reports: Overview of Activities, 1972 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 23)
  - University Development: Office of: Report of President Enarson, 1972 September-1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0042, Folder 24)
  - University Development: Office of: Report to President Enarson, 1972 September 1 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 1)
  - University Development: Office of: Reports, 1973 November-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 2)
  - University Development: Office of: Stadium Expansion, 1970 February-1972 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 3)
  - University Development: Office of: State Post-Secondary Education Commission, 1972 November-1973 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 4)
  - University District Organization, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 5)
  - University District Organization: Correspondence (Incl. Plans), 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 6)
  - University Hall: Dedication of New: Poem, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 7)
  - University Hospitals: The Bylaws, Rules and Regulations, 1970-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 8)
  - University Hospitals: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 9)
  - University Hospitals: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 10)
  - University Hospitals: Court of Claims, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 11)
  - University Hospitals: Executive Search Summary: Director of Hospital Administration, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 12)
  - University Hospitals: Guidance of: A Back Ground Paper, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 13)
  - University Hospitals: Income and Expenditures, 1971-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 14)
  - University Hospitals: Ohio Regional Medical Program, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 15)
  - University Hospital: Report of Examinations, 1970-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 16)
  - University Planning: Executive Director, 1972 September-1979 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 17)
  - University Press: Correspondence, 1972 January-1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 18)
  - University Publications: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 19)
  - University Research Association, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 20)
  - University School: Parent Opinion Report, 1958 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 21)
  - University School: Report of "Senior Trip" Committee, 1955-1971 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 22)
  - University Senate: Collective Bargaining: Ad Hoc Committee on, 1975 April 10 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 23)
  - University Senate: Correspondence and Resolutions, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 24)
  - University Senate: Correspondence and Resolutions, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 25)
  - University Senate: Correspondence and Resolutions, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 26)
  - University Senate: Correspondence and Resolutions, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 27)
  - University Senate: Correspondence and Resolutions, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 28)
  - University Senate: Correspondence and Resolutions, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 29)
  - University Senate: Faculty Compensation and Benefits Committee, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 30)
  - University Senate: Legislative Affairs Committee: Report, 1973 May 29 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 31)
  - University Senate: Mechanics Committee, 1975 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0043, Folder 32)
  - University Senate: Report of the Senate Select Committee on Women and Minorities, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 1)
  - University Senate: Secretary's Report, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 2)
  - University Senate: Secretary's Report, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 3)
  - University Senate: Secretary's Report, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 4)
  - University Senate: Secretary's Report, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 5)
  - University Senate: Steering Committee, 1972-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 6)
  - University of Texas: Cancer Center: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 7)
  - University Urban Studies: Memos (Incl. Seminar Speech), 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 8)
  - Urban Affairs, 1979 December-1980 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 9)
  - Utility and Renovation Projects, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 10)
  - Vandament, William E., 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 11)
  - Veterans Administration: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 12)
  - Veterinary Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 13)
  - Veterinary Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 14)
  - Veterinary Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 15)
  - Veterinary Medicine: College of: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 16)
  - Veterinary Medicine: College of: Document of Protest to Proposed Award of Contracts, 1973 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 17)
  - Vocational Education: Contracts and Agreements, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 18)
  - Vocational and Technical Education: Center for: Correspondence and Contracts, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 19)
  - Vocational Education: Proposal for Career Education Component of Applications Technology Satellite-F Project, 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 20)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education: Analysis and Planning for Improved Distribution of Nursing Personnel and Services, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 21)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education: Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 22)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education: National Task Force on Nursing, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 23)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education: Report: Information about NCHEMS (National Center for Higher Education Management Systems), undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0044, Folder 24)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education: Report: NCHMS: Center Profile, 1976 March 6 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 1)
  - Wingspread Recommendation: Foreign Student Recruitment, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 2)
  - Women's Liberation: A Proposal for a Center for Women's Studies, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 3)
  - Women and Minorities: Committee Report: By Recommendation, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 4)
  - Women and Minorities: Committee Report: By Respondent, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 5)
  - Women and Minorities Commission: Correspondence, 1975-1977 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 6)
  - Women and Minorities Commission: Correspondence, 1977 September-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 7)
  - Women's Studies: Office of: Correspondence, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 8)
  - Wright Airlines and Don Scott Field: Agreement, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0045, Folder 9)
- Accession Number UA.1985.0081, 1982; 0.02 Cubic feet; (1) file folder
  - Enarson regarding childhood, Cleveland State University, 1982 (Box Small Accessions 5)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Audiocassette
  - Notes submitted by Enarson for book by Underwood regarding the Enarson Years, 1982 (Box Small Accessions 5)
- Accession Number UA.1985.0053, 1971; 0.02 Cubic feet; (1) file folder
  - Presidential search committee, 1971 (Box Small Accessions 4)
- Accession Number UA.1985.0134, 1972-1983; 1.2 Cubic feet; (1) carton
  This series contains materials used by Professor Underwood in a biography of Harold Enarson.
  - Copies of speeches and statements by Enarson, 1972-1983 (Box UA.1985.0134.0001)
- Accession Number UA.1987.0202, 1976-1981; 1.4 Cubic feet; (1) carton, (1) 2.5" document box
  - SREB Speech, 1980 June 15 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - "Regulatory Influences" for ACE Book, 1981 May 15 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Presentations, 1979 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Athletics Article by HLE, 1980 Fall (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Cleveland City Club, 1981 January 16 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Contributions Council, 1981 January 27 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Columbus Rotary (Economic Impact), 1981 March 16 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - American College Health Association Speech, 1981 April 21 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Senate Speech, 1980 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Senate Speech, Follow Up Activities, 1980 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Senate Speech Background Info, 1980 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Ohio Public Expend. Council, 1980 September 17 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - HLE Report to Trustees, 1980 September 5 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Columbus Kiwanis speech, 1981 August 24 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Central State University Commencement, 1981 June 14 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Ohio State Commencement, 1981 June 12 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - University of Akron Commencement, 1981 May 24 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - UNM Leadership Speech, 1980 April 22 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Worthington High School Talk, 1980 April 16 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Coop Education (talk not given), 1980 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Ohio College Association Panel, 1980 May 12 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - East High School (Columbus) Talk, 1980 May 13 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Akron Roundtable Speech, 1980 June 19 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Akron Roundtable Background Information, undated (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Senate Speech- R.V. Esmand's Project File (2 folders), 1979 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Research Speech (Development of) President Enarson, 1978 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - President Enarson's UUF DC Speech, 1978 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - President Enarson's PTA Speech, 1979 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - President Enarson's WCA Speech, 1979 March 10 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - Senate Speech, 1978 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - President Enarson's Senate Speech, 1977 (Box UA.1987.0202.0001)
  - "Servants of the Public Interest" Speech, 1976 October 30 (Box UA.1987.0202.0002)
  - Enarson Speech Preparation, undated (Box UA.1987.0202.0002)
- Accession Number UA.1991.0034, 1977; 0.02 Cubic feet; (1) file folder
  - Freedom Foundation Award, 1977 (Box Small Accessions 13)
- Accession Number UA.1993.0184, 1978-1982; 6.0 Cubic feet; (5) cartons
  - Committee on Recognition--COPA February 1, 1981--Washington D.C., 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 1)
  - Argonne Universities Association, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 2)
  - Women and Minorities Committee, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 3)
  - Benefits (Insurance, Retirement, Annuities), 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 4)
  - Health Education Committee--AAU, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 5)
  - Council of Ten Folder--ABC matters, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 6)
  - Ohio College Association, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 7, 15)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 8)
  - Intercollegiate Conference (Western Conference), 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 9)
  - Agenda, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 10)
  - Inter-University Council of Ohio (IYC), 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 11)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 12-13)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 14)
  - Universities Research Association Incorporated, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Coal Research Laboratories Association, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Technology Transfer Organization (OTTO), 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 18)
  - Center for Lake Erie Area Research (CLEAR), 1979-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 19)
  - MUCIA, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 20)
  - State of Ohio, 1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 21)
  - University Planning, Executive Director of, 1980-1981 (Box UA.1993.0184.0001, Folder 22)